celinedion.com 2016-11-24

# 

Last Updated June 15, 2016

## WHO WE ARE

This privacy policy explains the personal information protection practices of BubbleUp, LLC., a company organized under the laws of Texas and whose principal office address is 9391 Grogan’s Mill Rd The Woodlands, TX 77380. Where we refer to "BubbleUp", “us” or "we", we mean BubbleUp, LLC.

As used in this privacy policy the term “Artist,” means Céline Dion.

We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy and the following sets out the basis on which any personal information we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be used and/or disclosed. Please read the text carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal information and how we will treat it.

## A SPECIAL NOTE TO CHILDREN UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE

YOU MUST BE 13 YEARS OF AGE OR OLDER TO REGISTER WITH OUR SITE. PLEASE DO NOT REGISTER IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE. There are certain web pages within our site that require users to be at least 13 years of age. This may mean that you will be unable to participate in some activities on the site.

## A SPECIAL NOTE TO PARENTS

Parents should supervise their children's online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers that help provide a child-friendly online environment. These tools can also prevent children from disclosing online their name, address, and other personal information without parental permission. 

## HOW WE COLLECT YOUR INFORMATION

(a) From you

We may collect and process personal information relating to you if you provide such personal information by filling in forms on our site or by you contacting us. This includes, but is not limited to, information provided at the time of registering to use (or become a member of) our site, subscribing to any services (for example, email or SMS newsletters), purchasing downloads or other products, posting material or requesting further services.

(b) By using cookies, web beacons or “clickstream data”

Some information may automatically be collected as you browse our site. Our web server automatically collects information known as "clickstream data," such as the domain name of the service providing you with Internet access, the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your browser type and version, operating system and platform, the average time spent on our site, pages viewed, information searched for, access times and other relevant statistics. 

In addition, we may use ‘cookies’ to collect information relating to your general internet usage. This information may include IP-addresses, browser version, number of visits and similar such information relating to your navigation of the internet and our site. A ‘cookie’ is a small text file that is placed on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalized service, for instance by storing information about your preferences and allowing us to recognize you when you return to our site. You may refuse to accept cookies by activating settings on your internet browser. However, please note that if you select such settings you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. 

Certain pages on our site may also contain “web beacons” (also known as Internet tags, pixel tags or clear GIFs). Web beacons may allow third parties to obtain non-personally identifiable information such as the IP address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the beacon appears, the URL of the page on which the beacon appears, the time the page containing the beacon was viewed, the type of browser used to view the page, and the information in cookies set by the third party. We use log files to store the data that is collected through web beacons.

## TRANSMISSION OF YOUR INFORMATION VIA THE INTERNET

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Any transmission is therefore made at your own risk.   
Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access. We use current industry standard technology to maintain the confidentiality and accuracy of the personal information you provide to us. We periodically review our security measures to ensure the security of your information. However, we cannot guarantee that any information you submit to us will be free from unauthorized third party intrusion. 

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share the password with anyone.

## HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

We use the information collected from our site in the following ways:

  * to ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.

  * to provide you with information, products or services that you have requested from us (or third parties, where appropriate) or which we or Artist feel may interest you.

  * to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us and, as permitted by law to perform credit checks, report or collect debts owed, or protect our rights or property, our site, or its users

  * to measure the use of our site and to administer and improve our site.

    * For example, we use clickstream data, web beacons and cookies only in the aggregate for these purposes. Any sharing of such data with unrelated third parties is on an anonymous basis. When we collect personal information, we may extract some of the information, such as demographic information and combine it with other information, such as clickstream data. This combined information is used and analyzed only at an aggregate level to help us or third parties understand trends and patterns.

  * to notify you about changes to our service.

  * to allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so, including:

    * Blogs and forums:  We ask each visitor who wishes to participate in blogs and forums on this site to provide an email address along with the visitor's screen name to access these functions. Except for the uses described in the paragraphs above, all such email addresses are used only to protect the security and integrity of the site, such as to take action against visitors who post inappropriate material or harass other visitors. You are responsible and are deemed to have consented to disclosure if you post your email address or other identifying information or content to a publicly viewable interactive site application such as a blog or forum

    * Contests: For contests conducted on our site, we use the personal information you provide only for the purpose of contacting you if you win a prize and sending the prize to you. We do not use contact information contained in contest entries to create mailing lists or for any other purpose without your consent. All contests that are held on this site are limited to persons above a certain age. Accordingly, we ask each contestant to provide year of birth, as well as name, address, and e-mail address. If the year provided indicates that the contestant is underage, the information submitted is deleted. Please refer to the specific age requirements for each contest as rules may vary from contest to contest.

  * To help protect you and others, we monitor use of our sites, and we use the information we collect, including personal information, to identify fraudulent activities and transactions; prevent abuse of and investigate and/or seek prosecution for any potential threats to or misuse of our sites; ensure compliance with the applicable terms of service and this privacy policy; investigate violations of or enforce these agreements; and otherwise to protect the rights and property of Artist and BubbleUp, and Artist’s and BubbleUp’s respective partners, and customers.  Monitoring may result in the collection, recording, and analysis of online activity or communications through our sites.  If you do not consent to these conditions, you must discontinue your use of our site.

## WITH WHOM WE SHARE YOUR DATA

Subject to the other terms of this policy, and where appropriate, we may share your personal information with the following:

  1. Artist and Artist’s Partners

Personal information collected on this site may be shared with the Artist, those companies organized to directly represent Artist in the exercise of her business interests, her management, and in connection with promotional and marketing activities related to Artist that may be of interest to you, her record label and service providers. These parties have agreed with us to use personal information of site visitors only for the purposes of carrying out these operations and/or activities.

  2. Other third parties

We may transfer, sell or assign any data, including personally identifiable data, to third parties, only in connection with the sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation of BubbleUp, LLC, or any part of it. 

   We and/or Artist (or entities working on Artist’s behalf) may share with others, at our and/or Artist’s discretion, certain aggregate statistical data about purchases and the use of our content, which data may include demographic data such as the age range and/or geographic location of groups of users. No personal information (such as names or email addresses) will be identifiable from such statistics.

  3. In special circumstances

We may disclose personal information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this data is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with the rights or property of those described above in paragraph (a) or (b). We may also disclose your personal information when we believe in good faith that the law requires us to do so.

## YOUR RIGHT TO OBTAIN, CHANGE OR REMOVE YOUR INFORMATION

You can opt out of receiving any further messages from BubbleUp or anyone with whom we share your data (as described above) at any time by following the unsubscribe instructions in any message sent to you, or by contacting us by email at [info@bubbleup.net](mailto:webmaster@sonymusic.ca).

You have the right to access the personal information we hold about you. To view the personal information we hold about you or if you have any questions or comments concerning this Privacy Policy, please write to us at our principal address provided at the beginning of this privacy policy, attention: Privacy Officer. You can also send an email to [info@bubbleup.net](mailto:webmaster@sonymusic.ca). If you find any errors in your personal information, please contact us and we will try to correct the error or explain how you can correct it.

## OTHER WEBSITES

Our site may contain links to other websites which are outside our control and are not covered by this privacy policy. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect and process information from you in a way which is different to how we do so. Please review the privacy policy notices on those sites for further details.

## THIRD PARTY COOKIES

Some of the advertisements on this site may be generated by third party partners. These third parties may use their own "cookies" to track how many unique users have seen, or click on, a particular advertisement. These cookies cannot be used to identify you as an individual, and are used only for statistical purposes or, for example, to provide advertisements that are more relevant to your preferences.   
BubbleUp is not responsible for third party cookies, other than allowing them to be served via our websites. However, we may use statistical information arising from these third party cookies that is provided to us, if at all, by such third parties to improve the targeting of advertisements to users (see also 'How we collect your information' above).  
If you wish to block third party cookies, you can do so in your browser's security settings.

## CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

We may modify, alter or otherwise update this privacy policy at any time. We will indicate any changes by updating the date at the top of the policy. We encourage you to review this policy from time to time.

## AU SUJET DE BUBBLEUP, LLC.

Cette politique de confidentialité précise les pratiques en matière de protection des renseignements personnels mises en œuvre par BubbleUp, LLC., société constituée selon les lois du Texas et dont le siège social est situé au 9391 Grogan’s Mill Rd The Woodlands, TX 77380. Les termes « BubbleUp », « nous », « notre » ou « nos » désignent BubbleUp, LLC.

Lorsqu’il est utilisé dans cette politique de confidentialité, le terme « artiste » désigne Céline Dion.

Nous nous engageons à protéger et à respecter votre droit à la confidentialité, et les dispositions suivantes précisent les contextes dans lesquels les renseignements personnels que nous recueillons à votre propos ou que vous nous fournissez sont utilisés et/ou divulgués. Veuillez lire ce texte attentivement afin de comprendre nos positions, nos méthodes de fonctionnement et nos modes de gestion à l’égard de vos renseignements personnels.

## NOTE À L’INTENTION DES ENFANTS DE MOINS DE 13 ANS

VOUS DEVEZ AVOIR 13 ANS OU PLUS POUR VOUS INSCRIRE AUPRÈS DE NOTRE SITE. NE VOUS Y INSCRIVEZ PAS SI VOUS N’AVEZ PAS ENCORE 13 ANS. Certaines des pages web de notre site ne peuvent être consultées que par des personnes de 13 ans ou plus. Ainsi, vous pourriez être incapables de participer à certaines des activités offertes par le site.

## NOTE À L’INTENTION DES PARENTS

Les parents sont invités à superviser les activités en ligne de leurs enfants et à utiliser les outils de contrôle parental offerts par des services en ligne ou des fabricants de logiciels et qui permettent d’offrir un environnement en ligne adapté aux enfants. Ces outils peuvent aussi empêcher que les enfants divulguent leurs noms, leurs adresses et leurs autres renseignements personnels en ligne sans l’autorisation de leurs parents.

## MÉTHODES DE COLLECTE DE RENSEIGNEMENTS

a) Directement de vous

Nous pouvons recueillir et traiter des renseignements personnels qui vous concernent si vous nous les fournissez lorsque vous remplissez des formulaires sur notre site ou que vous communiquez avec nous. Ceci comprend, notamment, les renseignements fournis lors de votre inscription à titre d’utilisateur (ou de membre) de notre site, l’abonnement aux services (par exemple, les infolettres par courriel ou par SMS), l’achat de matériel à télécharger ou d’autres produits, l’affichage d’éléments ou les demandes de services.

b) Grâce à des fichiers témoins, des pixels invisibles ou des « données de parcours »

Certains renseignements peuvent être recueillis automatiquement quand vous naviguez sur notre site. Par exemple, notre serveur web recueille automatiquement des renseignements appelées « données de parcours », comme le nom de domaine de votre fournisseur de services internet, l’adresse IP utilisée pour mettre votre ordinateur en communication avec l’internet, votre type de navigateur et sa version, votre système et votre plateforme d’exploitation, le temps moyen passé sur nos sites, les pages consultées, les renseignements recherchés, vos heures d’accès et d’autres statistiques pertinentes. Nous pouvons aussi utiliser des « fichiers témoins » (ou « cookies ») pour recueillir des renseignements au sujet de vos habitudes générales de navigation. Cela peut comprendre des adresses IP, la version de votre navigateur, votre nombre de visites et d’autres renseignements similaires concernant votre navigation sur l’internet et dans notre site. Un « fichier témoin » est un petit fichier texte placé dans le lecteur de disque dur de votre ordinateur. Les fichiers témoins nous aident à améliorer notre site et à vous donner un service personnalisé de meilleure qualité, par exemple, en stockant des renseignements au sujet de vos préférences, ou qui nous permettent de vous reconnaître quand vous revenez sur notre site. Vous pouvez refuser d’accepter les fichiers témoins en configurant vos préférences dans votre navigateur internet en conséquence. Veuillez noter cependant qu’en choisissant de tels réglages, vous pourriez ne pas être en mesure d’accéder à certaines parties de notre site.

Quelques-unes des pages de notre site peuvent contenir des « pixels invisibles » (également nommés des marqueurs internet, des pixels-espions ou des GIF invisibles). Les pixels invisibles servent à des tiers à obtenir des renseignements non personnels comme l’adresse IP de l’ordinateur ayant téléchargé la page contenant le marqueur, l’adresse URL de cette page, le moment auquel le marqueur a été affiché, le type de navigateur utilisé pour afficher la page et les renseignements contenus dans les fichiers témoins installés par un tiers. Nous utilisons des fichiers de journalisation afin de stocker les données recueillies grâce à des pixels invisibles.

## TRANSMISSION DE VOS RENSEIGNEMENTS PAR INTERNET

Malheureusement, la transmission de renseignements par internet n’est pas entièrement sécurisée. Cette transmission se fait donc à vos propres risques. Une fois vos renseignements reçus, nous utilisons des procédures et des fonctions de sécurité rigoureuses dans le but d’empêcher tout accès non autorisé. Nous utilisons des moyens technologiques répondant aux normes actuelles de l’industrie afin de protéger la confidentialité et l’exactitude des renseignements personnels que vous nous confiez. Nous révisons périodiquement nos mesures de sécurité afin de nous assurer de la protection de vos renseignements. Cela étant, nous ne pouvons pas garantir que les renseignements que vous nous confiez ne feront jamais l’objet d’une intrusion non autorisée par un tiers. Lorsque nous vous attribuons (ou que vous choisissez) un mot de passe afin de vous permettre d’accéder à certaines parties de notre site, vous avez la responsabilité d’en protéger la confidentialité. Nous vous demandons de ne jamais le révéler à un tiers.

## COMMENT NOUS UTILISONS VOS RENSEIGNEMENTS

Nous utilisons les renseignements recueillis dans notre site comme suit:

  * Afin de nous assurer que le contenu du site est présenté de la manière la plus efficace possible pour vous et votre ordinateur.

  * Afin de vous fournir l’information, les produits ou les services que vous nous demandez (ou que vous demandez à des tiers, s’il y a lieu) ou que l’artiste ou nous pensons que vous trouverez intéressants.

  * Afin de respecter nos obligations contractuelles envers vous et, si la loi le permet, afin d’effectuer des vérifications de solvabilité, de rapporter ou de recouvrer des créances ou afin de protéger nos droits, nos biens, notre site ou ses utilisateurs.

  * Afin de mesurer l’utilisation de notre site, de le gérer et de l’améliorer.

    * Par exemple, nous utilisons des données de parcours, des pixels invisibles et fichiers témoins agrégés à ces seules fins. Tout partage de données avec des tiers indépendants se fait sur une base anonyme. Lorsque nous recueillons des renseignements personnels, nous pouvons en extraire une partie, comme des données démographiques, et les combiner avec d’autres renseignements, comme des données de parcours. Ces renseignements combinés sont utilisés et analysés seulement d’un point de vue global afin de nous permettre, ou de permettre à des tiers, de comprendre les tendances et les comportements types qui s’en dégagent.

  * Afin de vous aviser des changements à nos services.

  * Afin de vous permettre de profiter des fonctionnalités interactives de nos services, lorsque vous le souhaitez, y compris:

    * Blogues et forums: Nous demandons à tous les visiteurs qui souhaitent participer à des blogues ou à des forums offerts sur notre site de fournir une adresse électronique, ainsi qu’un pseudonyme avant d’y accéder. Mises à part les utilisations décrites aux paragraphes précédents, ces adresses électroniques ne servent qu’à assurer la sécurité et l’intégrité du site, par exemple, en prenant des mesures contre les visiteurs qui affichent des messages inappropriés ou qui harcèlent d’autres visiteurs. Vous êtes responsable de (et êtes considéré-e avoir consenti à) la divulgation de votre adresse électronique et autres renseignements personnels lorsque vous les affichez par le biais d’une application de site interactif publiquement accessible comme un blogue ou un forum.

    * Concours: En ce qui concerne les concours sur notre site, nous utilisons les renseignements personnels que vous nous fournissez aux seules fins de communiquer avec vous si vous gagnez un prix et de vous le faire parvenir. Nous n’utilisons pas de coordonnées fournies afin de participer à un concours afin de créer des listes d’envoi ou à d’autres fins sans obtenir un consentement préalable. Les concours lancés sur ce site sont ouverts en fonction d’un âge minimum. C’est pourquoi nous demandons à chaque participant de préciser son année de naissance, ainsi que son nom, son adresse et son adresse électronique. Si l’année indique que le participant n’a pas atteint l’âge minimal requis, les renseignements soumis sont supprimés. Veuillez consulter les exigences de chaque concours en matière d’âge puisque les règles peuvent varier d’un concours à l’autre.

  * Afin de vous protéger et de protéger les tiers, nous contrôlons l’utilisation de nos sites et nous utilisons les renseignements que nous recueillons, y compris les renseignements personnels, afin de déceler des activités ou des opérations de nature frauduleuse ; d’empêcher les abus, d’enquêter et/ou d’intenter des poursuites en cas de menaces potentielles ou d’utilisation inappropriée de nos sites ; de nous assurer de l’observation des conditions d’utilisation applicables et de cette politique de confidentialité ; de faire enquête à ce sujet et d’appliquer nos politiques ; et d’agir autrement afin de protéger les droits et les biens de l’artiste et de BubbleUp, ainsi que ceux de leurs partenaires et clients respectifs. Cela peut nécessiter la surveillance, l’enregistrement ou l’analyse d’activités ou de communications en ligne sur nos sites. Si vous ne consentez pas à ces modalités, vous devez arrêter d’utiliser notre site.

## AVEC QUI PARTAGEONS-NOUS VOS DONNÉES ?

Sous réserve des autres dispositions de cette politique, s’il y a lieu, nous pouvons partager vos renseignements personnels avec les personnes suivantes:

  1. L’artiste et ses partenaires

Les renseignements personnels recueillis sur ce site peuvent être partagés avec l’artiste, les sociétés constituées dans le but de représenter directement ses intérêts commerciaux, sa gérance ou ses activités de promotion et de mise en marché pouvant vous intéresser, ainsi que sa maison de disques et des fournisseurs de services. Ces parties ont convenu avec nous d’utiliser les renseignements personnels des visiteurs de notre site seulement dans le cadre de ces opérations et/ou activités.

  1. Les autres personnes

Nous pouvons transmettre, vendre ou céder des données, y compris des renseignements personnels à des tiers seulement dans le cadre de la vente, la fusion, la consolidation, le changement de contrôle, le transfert d’une partie substantielle des biens, la réorganisation ou la liquidation, en tout ou en partie, de BubbleUp, LLC.

Nous et/ou l’artiste (ou des entreprises agissant au nom de l’artiste) pouvons partager avec des tiers, à notre discrétion et/ou à celle de l’artiste, certaines données statistiques agrégées au sujet des achats et de l’utilisation de notre contenu, qui peuvent comprendre des renseignements démographiques comme la tranche d’âge et/ou la situation géographique de groupes d’utilisateurs. Les renseignements personnels (comme les noms ou les adresses électroniques) ressortiront de ces statistiques.

  1. Dans des situations particulières

Nous pouvons divulguer des renseignements personnels dans des situations particulières, lorsque nous avons des motifs de croire que cette divulgation est nécessaire afin d’identifier une personne, de communiquer avec elle ou d’intenter des poursuites contre elle, car elle cause un préjudice ou nuit (intentionnellement ou non) aux droits ou aux biens des personnes énumérées aux paragraphes a) ou b) ci-dessus. Nous pourrions également avoir à divulguer vos renseignements personnels si nous croyons de bonne foi que la loi nous y oblige.

## VOTRE DROIT D’OBTENIR, DE MODIFIER OU DE FAIRE SUPPRIMER VOS RENSEIGNEMENTS

Vous pouvez en tout temps vous retirer d’une liste d’envoi de BubbleUp ou d’un tiers avec qui vos données sont partagées (de la façon précisée ci-dessus) en suivant les instructions de désabonnement reproduites dans les messages qui vous sont transmis ou en communiquant avec nous par courriel à [info@bubbleup.net](mailto:webmaster@sonymusic.ca).

Vous avez le droit d’accéder aux renseignements personnels que nous détenons à votre sujet. Pour les voir ou pour toute question au sujet de cette Politique de confidentialité, veuillez écrire à l’adresse de notre siège social mentionnée au début de cette politique, aux soins de notre responsable de la protection des renseignements personnels (Privacy Officer). Vous pouvez aussi nous faire parvenir un courriel à[info@bubbleup.net](mailto:webmaster@sonymusic.ca). Si vous trouvez des erreurs dans vos renseignements personnels, veuillez communiquer avec nous et nous tenterons de les corriger ou de vous expliquer comment le faire.

## AUTRES SITES WEB

Notre site peut proposer des liens à d’autres sites web hors de notre contrôle et qui ne sont pas visés par cette Politique de confidentialité. Si vous accédez à de tels sites en utilisant les liens fournis, leurs exploitants pourront recueillir et traiter vos renseignements avec d’autres méthodes que les nôtres. Veuillez prendre connaissance des avis concernant leurs politiques de confidentialité pour de plus amples renseignements.

## FICHIERS TÉMOINS APPARTENANT À DES TIERS

Certains des messages publicitaires contenus sur notre site peuvent être générés par nos partenaires. Ces tiers peuvent utiliser leurs propres « fichiers témoins » afin de déterminer combien d’utilisateurs uniques ont vu ou cliqué sur un message en particulier. Leurs fichiers témoins ne peuvent pas servir à vous identifier et sont seulement utilisés à des fins statistiques ou, par exemple, pour vous proposer des messages publicitaires correspondant mieux vos préférences.

BubbleUp n’est pas responsable des fichiers témoins appartenant à des tiers, auxquels il a seulement donné la permission de vous joindre par le biais de nos sites web. Nous pouvons cependant utiliser les données statistiques générées par les fichiers témoins qu’ils nous fournissent, le cas échéant, afin d’améliorer le ciblage des publicités aux utilisateurs (consultez également la rubrique « Méthodes de collecte de renseignements » ci-dessus).

Si vous souhaitez bloquer les fichiers témoins des tiers, vous pouvez le faire dans les réglages de sécurité de votre navigateur.

## MODIFICATIONS À NOTRE POLITIQUE DE CONFIDENTIALITÉ

Nous pouvons modifier cette Politique de confidentialité ou autrement la mettre à jour. Nous annoncerons les modifications en mettant à jour la date précisée au haut de la politique. Nous vous encourageons à relire cette politique de temps à autre.
